(Leonard:)He lives in the same room
where his bassinet was.
(Beverley:)Both selective mutism and an inability
to separate from one's mother...
(Beverley:)...can stem from a pathological fear
of women.
(Beverley:)It might explain why the two of you have
created an ersatz homosexual marriage...
(Beverley:)...to satisfy your need for intimacy.
(Howard:)Say what?
[WHISPERS INAUDIBLY]
(Howard:)That's basically what I just said.
(Leonard:)You brought your husband to work,
you know the rules.
[AS JAR JAR BINKS]
Meesa thinking yousa looking pretty sad...
(Leonard:)...now too, betcha, betcha.
Leonard, it's 1:00. Weren't you going
to show me your laboratory at 1:00?
(Leonard:)No hurry, Mother. Tell them more
about their secret love for each other.
But it's 1:00. You were going to show me
your laboratory at 1:00.
Her reasoning is unassailable. It is 1:00.
(Leonard:)Fine. Let's go.
(Leonard:)I think you'll find my work
pretty interesting.
(Leonard:)I'm attempting to replicate...